A Therapeutic New Comedy
Prime is a comedy, drama, romance film directed by Ben Younger.
A career driven professional from Manhattan is wooed by a young
painter, who also happens to be the son of her psychoanalyst.
Rafi Gardet, played by Uma Thurman.
Lisa Metzger, played by Meryl Streep.
David Bloomberg, played by Bryan Greenberg.
Morris, played by Jon Abrahams.
Randall, played by Zak Orth.
Catherine, played by Annie Parisse.
Prime is a 2005 American romantic comedy-drama film starring
Uma Thurman, Meryl Streep, and Bryan Greenberg.
It was written and directed by Ben Younger.
The film grossed $67.9 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of new york city, lovesickness,
jealousy, love of one's life, therapist.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.